(Sheldon:)Hold on.
Do you honestly expect me to believe
social protocol dictates...
(Sheldon:)...we break our backs helping Wolowitz
move, and he only need buy us a pizza?
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, that really is how it works.
(Sheldon:)You're tricking me.
(Sheldon:)- Tell me the truth, what do we get?
- Ha.
(Leonard:)Raj, help me out here.
(Raj:)You get to choose
between a mountain bike or a PS3.
(Sheldon:)I knew it.
- PS3, definitely PS3.
- Mm-hm.
(Sheldon:)Who would pick a mountain bike?
HOWARD: Enough with the guilt, Ma.
We'll still see each other.
(Howard(voice from inside):)I'll come over every night
and have dinner with you.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
The hell you will!
(Howard's Mother(voice):)What am I running here,
a fancy restaurant?
(Howard's Mother(voice):)Does this look like Olive Garden?
HOWARD:
Okay, I get it, you're angry.
You don't wanna see
your little bird leave the nest.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Little bird? You're almost 30!